Hmm.
う む
Looks like it'll fit in.
入りそう
Please move your body.
体を動かしてください
You can take it out.
抜いていいよ
Did you enter?
入った?
A little while ago, I tried standing up and spreading it out.
ちょっと前に, 立ち広げてやってみて
have a relationship
縁を持ってみ
hand...
て...
Just the thickness and ribbon.
太しさとリボンだけで
It's a little scary.
ちょっとやばい
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待ってください
You're sorry, aren't you?
申 し訳ないでしょ
I guess I'll do it...
ちょっと俺がやろうか...
Should Donna-chan do it?
Donna-chanがやろうか?
feel ill?
気持ち悪い?
dosage?
dosesie?
Are you stupid?
バカして?
Should I do it because it's a waste?
もったいないからやろうか?
what up?
どうした?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかったですか?
No, that's amazing.
いいや、すばすばしいですね
I'm sorry, but I've had enough.
な かたししちゃいましたけど、 もう結構、
Turn around.
もぐり返しして
That's amazing,
すごいな、
It's come out again.
また 出てきちゃったもん
Please go back to sleep.
もう一度寝てください